NIKOLA NEDELJKOVIC

WordPress expert

Personal information



✓ nnedeljkovic8@gmail.com

Vojvode Vlahovica 35e, Belgrade, Serbia

in <u>Nikola Nedeljkovic</u>

nnedeljkovic8

Skills

- Creating well-designed, responsive

WordPress websites by utilizing Page

Builders and corresponding plugins;

- Monitoring and improving website performance;
- Basic knowledge in HTML and CSS;
- Familiar with PHP and phpMyAdmin;
- Familiar with SEO and proactive sitemap

submission;

- Basic knowledge in Adobe Photoshop;
- Excellent knowledge in Canva;
- Excellent knowledge in MS Office;
- Familiar with Facebook Business

Manager;

Education

- <u>IT Bootcamp</u>, WordPress course, 07/2022-09/2022;
- Faculty of Political Sciences, Journalism and Communications, University of Belgrade, 2010-2015;
- Faculty of Economics, University of Belgrade, 2007-2009;
- High School "Bora Stankovic", Vranje 2003-2007.

About

After graduation, I worked as a web journalist and social media manager. Over the past years, I have recognized the potential of websites for improving business results and creating a positive image for companies and entrepreneurs. Inspired to learn how to create attractive and functional websites, I decided to apply for the IT Bootcamp and complete the Web development (WordPress) course.

Work experience

Motus media (2020-2022)

- Writing and translating agency news, reports, and articles;
- Photo editing;
- Site administration and publishing content on Facebook pages;
- Content writing.

Rec defektologa/Facebook and Instagram page (2020-2022)

- Content writing;
- Facebook and Instagram page administration;
- Creation of visuals for publication on the pages;
- Facebook Ads.

Desk plus (2019-2020)

- Writing and translating agency news, reports, and articles;
- Photo editing;
- Preparation and equipping texts for publication on the portals Telegraf.rs, Index.hr, Klix.ba.

Istorijski zabavnik (2016-2019)

- Writing reports, interviews, and articles;
- Photo processing;
- Site administration and publishing content on social media.

Languages

- Serbian (native)
- English (intermediate)

Hobbies







